{
    "quizTitle": "Data Divers ",
    "quizSynopsis": "How familiar are you with MySQL and Mongo Databases? Select the correct answer to these ten common technical interview questions and see where you stand.",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What are CRUD operations? ",
        "answers": [
          "Create, Read, Update, and Delete ",
          "Create, Route, Update, and Delete",
          "Create, Read, Update, and Document",
          "Create, Read, UnMount, and Delete "
        ],
        "questionType": "text",
        "correctAnswer": "1"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "JSON",
          "BSON",
          "MSON",
          "DSON"
        ],
        "question": "How is data stored in MongoDB?",
        "questionType": "text",
        "correctAnswer": "2"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "VARCHAR",
          "TEXT",
          "BLOB",
          "STRING"
        ],
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a MySQL string type?",
        "correctAnswer": "4",
        "questionType": "text"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "INNER",
          "LEFT",
          "MIDDLE",
          "FULL"
        ],
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of MySQL join?",
        "questionType": "text",
        "correctAnswer": "3"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "drop.db.collection()",
          "db.drop.collection()",
          "db.collection.drop()",
          "db.table.drop()"
        ],
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "What is the syntax to drop a collection on MongoDB",
        "correctAnswer": "3"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "It creates a unique index",
          "It is always the first field in documents",
          "It won't contain any arrays",
          "It needs to be added manually"
        ],
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "What is NOT true about the _id field in MongoDB",
        "correctAnswer": "4"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "Find Databases;",
          "Show Databases;",
          "List Databases;",
          "Read Databases;"
        ],
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "Which command will list all databases in MySql?",
        "correctAnswer": "2"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "8080",
          "3000",
          "3360",
          "3306"
        ],
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "What is MySql's default port number?",
        "correctAnswer": "4"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "use <db_name>",
          "create <db_name>",
          "switch <db_name>",
          "index <db_name>"
        ],
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "Which command will create a MongDB Database?",
        "correctAnswer": "1"
      },
      {
        "answers": [
          "CREATE ROW",
          "CREATE INTO",
          "INSERT INTO ",
          "INSERT AFTER "
        ],
        "questionType": "text",
        "question": "Which MySQl statement will add a new row to a table?",
        "correctAnswer": "3"
      }
    ]
  }